彻夜难眠
编剧：史蒂文·莫法特
还是不敢相信 我竟然有权利养他
I still can't believe I'm allowed him.
他是你儿子啊
He's your son.
我就是想说这个
That's what I'm talking about.
我是说 谁批准这事的
I mean, who authorized this?
这是我遇到的最可怕的事情了
It's the single most terrifying thing that's ever happened to me.
我是说 我把他碰坏了怎么办
I mean, what if I break him?
最好尽力别让它发生
Yeah, you best try not to do that.
你好吗 小家伙
You all right, mate?
看吧 没反应
See? Nothing!
他没事的 他很爱你的
He's fine. He loves you.
看到了吗
See?
嘿
Hey!
只是每次我看着他的眼睛
It's just when I look into his eyes,
我接下来的六十年可能做错的事
I see everything I'm going to do wrong
就全都浮现到我的眼前
for the next 60 years reflected back at me.
你会是一个好爸爸的
You're going to be an amazing dad,
因为你是一个很棒的人
'cause you're an amazing man.
好的
Okay.
嗯 挺好的
Huh? That's good.
还没坏
Still not broken.
又一个 你听说这些消失的人了吗
Another one. Have you seen all these people disappearing?
你能完全确定吗
And you're absolutely sure about this?
我和他单独放在一起
Me and him on our own
整整一周
for a whole weekend?
当然了 最坏能坏到哪儿去呢
Of course, what is the worst that could happen?
别说这句话
Don't ever say that!
说了这句话就一定会发生坏事
If you say that, terrible things will happen.
你没看见电影里都这样吗
Have you never seen a film?
来吧 该洗澡了
Come on, it's his bath time.
什么 我们昨天才给他洗过
What? We literally just did that yesterday.
噢 拜托 别再大惊小怪了
Oh, for God's sake, stop your fussing.
一切都会没事的
Everything is going to be fine.
只是湿个手肘而已 又不是世界末日
It's wet elbows, not the end of the world. Come on.
好吧 我们带你去洗澡了
Fine. Let's get you in the bath.
你不在的时候我也得给他洗澡吗
Do I have to bath him while you're gone?